Peter Wexler papers 1965 - ongoing
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Papers., Series:I
  - New York Philharmonic. Horizons. - Contracts. 1986 (Box 34)
  - New York Philharmonic. Horizons. - Budget. 1986 (Box 34)
  - New York Philharmonic. Horizons. - Business. 1986 (Box 34)
  - New York Philharmonic. Horizons. - Memorandum. 1986 (Box 34)
  - American History Workshop. Albany UCP. 1986 (Box 34)
  - American History Workshop. Albany UCP. - Photos. 1986 (Box 34)
  - American History Workshop. Albany UCP. - Signs. 1986 (Box 34)
  - American History Workshop. Albany UCP. - Brochures. 1986 (Box 34)
  - American History Workshop. Albany UCP. - Final Exhibition Text and Video Script. 1986 (Box 34)
  - American History Workshop. Albany UCP. - Rough Video Script. 1986 (Box 34)
  - American History Workshop. Albany UCP. - Walking Tour Script. 1986 (Box 34)
  - Hopeman Brothers Inc. Canopy Lighting. 1986 (Box 34)
  - Hopeman Brothers Inc. Canopy Lighting. - Photos. 1986 (Box 34)
  - Hopeman Brothers Inc. Canopy Lighting. - Business. 1986 (Box 34)
  - Hopeman Brothers Inc. Canopy Lighting. - Background. 1986 (Box 34)
  - Hopeman Brothers Inc. Canopy Lighting. - Canopy Lighing. Background. 1986 (Box 34)
  - Hopeman Brothers Inc. Canopy Lighting. - Canopy Lighting. Test. Original. 1986 (Box 34)
  - Hopeman Brothers Inc. Canopy Lighting. - Canopy Lighting. As Submitted 9/2/86. 1986 (Box 34)
  - Hopeman Brothers Inc. Canopy Lighting. - Press and Public Relations. 1986 (Box 34)
  - Hopeman Brothers Inc. Canopy Lighting. - Transmittals. 1986 (Box 34)
  - Hopeman Brothers Inc. Canopy Lighting. - Records of Meetings and Calls. 1986 (Box 34)
  - Hopeman Brothers Inc. Canopy Lighting. - Research. 1986 (Box 34)
  - Hopeman Brothers Inc. Canopy Lighting. - Memorandum. 1986 (Box 34)
  - New School Computer Class. Hal Tine'. 1986 (Box 35)
  - Criswell Development Company. Cooling Tower. 1986 (Box 35)
  - Criswell Development Company. Cooling Tower. - Memorandum. 1986 (Box 35)
  - Criswell Development Company. Cooling Tower. - Business. 1986 (Box 35)
  - Criswell Development Company. Cooling Tower. - Research. 1986 (Box 35)
  - Criswell Development Company. Cooling Tower. - Photos and slides. 1986 (Box 35)
  - Dun and Bradstreet. New Vision. 1986 (Box 35)
  - Dun and Bradstreet. New Vision. - Memorandum. 1986 (Box 35)
  - Dun and Bradstreet. New Vision. - Film and Video. 1986 (Box 35)
  - New York State. 1986 (Box 35)
  - New York State. - Business. 1986 (Box 35)
  - New York State. - Memorandum. 1986 (Box 35)
  - American History Workshop. Barge Proposal. 1986 (Box 35)
  - American History Workshop. Barge Proposal. - Photographs. Slides. 1986. 1986 (Box 35)
  - American History Workshop. Barge Proposal. - Proposal. 1986 (Box 35)
  - American History Workshop. Barge Proposal. - Memorandum. 1986 (Box 35)
  - National Symphony. Rostropovich Gala. Slava Gala. 1987 (Box 35)
  - National Symphony. Rostropovich Gala. Slava Gala. - Memorandum. 1987 (Box 35)
  - National Symphony. Rostropovich Gala. Slava Gala. - Business. 1987 (Box 35)
  - National Symphony. Rostropovich Gala. Slava Gala. - Budget. 1987 (Box 35)
  - National Symphony. Rostropovich Gala. Slava Gala. - Artist Information Sheets. 1987 (Box 35)
  - National Symphony. Rostropovich Gala. Slava Gala. - Design. Photos. 1987 (Box 35)
  - National Symphony. Rostropovich Gala. Slava Gala. - Press and Public Relations. 1987 (Box 35)
  - National Symphony. Rostropovich Gala. Slava Gala. - Program. 1987 (Box 35)
  - National Symphony. Rostropovich Gala. Slava Gala. - Research. 1987 (Box 35)
  - Mark Taper Forum. Terra Nova. Japan. 1987 (Box 35)
  - Mark Taper Forum. Terra Nova. Japan. - Script with cues. 1987 (Box 35)
  - Mark Taper Forum. Terra Nova. Japan. - Theatres. 1987 (Box 35)
  - Mark Taper Forum. Terra Nova. Japan. - Memorandum. 1987 (Box 35)
  - Mark Taper Forum. Terra Nova. Japan. - Business. 1987 (Box 35)
  - Mark Taper Forum. Terra Nova. Japan. - Press and Public Relations. 1987 (Box 35)
  - Mark Taper Forum. Terra Nova. Japan. - Design. 1987 (Box 35)
  - Mark Taper Forum. Terra Nova. Japan. - Research. 1987 (Box 35)
  - Mark Taper Forum. Terra Nova. Japan. - Projection. 1987 (Box 35)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Iron Ghost. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Red Talkers. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Research Paintings. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Symphony Back Wall. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Nez Perce. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Elk Song. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Ceremonial Birds. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - The Offering. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - The Escape. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Storyboard. Background Xerox. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Storyboard. Background Original. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Storyboard. Credits Revised. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Storyboard. Credits. Titles As Submitted. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Storyboards. Revised. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Storyboards. 3rd mov. as submitted. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Storyboards. 3rd mov. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Storyboards. 2nd mov. as submitted. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Storyboards. 2nd mov. revised. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Storyboards. 2nd mov. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Storyboards. 1st mov. as submitted. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Storyboards. 1st mov. revised. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Rough Storyboards. 1st mov. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Blank Storyboards. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Photos. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Complete Storyboards. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Script Storyboards. As Submitted. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Rough Storyboards. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Score. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Sheet Music. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Photo Information. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Media and Stage. 8/23/85. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Press and Public Relations. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Business. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - POPF Business. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Memorandum. 1987 (Box 36)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Pletka Project. Photos. - Transmittals. 1987 (Box 36)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Engineering Proposal. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Research. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Seating 1. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Seating 2. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Bandshell II. Design. Office. Dressing Room. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Press and Public Relations. 1986. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Bandshell II. Seating. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Bandshell II. Lighting. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Bandshell II. Design. Control Truck. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Bandshell II. Design. Stage. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Bandshell II. Design. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Bandshell II. Sun Analysis. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Bandshell II. Site Electrical Reg. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Bandshell II. Budget Analysis. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Summerstage 1987. Recommendations. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - As Submitted 11/14. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Memorandum. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Bandshell II. Vendor Book. Original Paperwork. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Physical Design. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Original Paperwork. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Business. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Transmittals. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Rick Grey Critique. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. 1986-1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. - Bandshell. 1986. 1986 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. - Summerstage 1987. 1987 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. - Summerstage 1987. - Other Vendors. 1987 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. - Summerstage 1987. - Sound. 1987 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. - Summerstage 1987. - Lighting. 1987 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. - Summerstage 1987. - Scenic Design. 1987 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. - Summerstage 1988. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. - Summerstage 1988. - Trucking. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. - Summerstage 1988. - Lighting Design Paperwork. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. - Summerstage 1988. - Lighting. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. - Summerstage 1988. - Sound. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. - Summerstage 1988. - Physical Design. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. - Mall Renovation Plan. 1987. 1987 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell. - Mall Renovation Consultants. 1988. 1988 (Box 37)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. 1988 (Box 38)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Bandshell II. 1988 (Box 38)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Pricing Vendor and Backup Book. 1. 1988 (Box 38)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Pricing Vendor and Backup Book. 2. 1988 (Box 38)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Schematic Design for a Seasonal Performance stage at CP. 1. 1988 (Box 38)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Schematic Design for a Seasonal Performance stage at CP. 2. 1988 (Box 38)
  - City of New York. Bandshell II. - Meeting and Phone Log. 1988 (Box 38)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Budget Discussion Book Revised. 2/28/86. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Budget Discussion Book Revised. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Proposal. 1985. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Business. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Business. End Loader. 2. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Business. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Memorandum. 2. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Memorandum. End Loader. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Furniture and Fixtures. End Loader. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Seating and Fixtures. End Loader. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Seating Options. End Loader. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Photos. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Ferry I Side Loader. Meeting and Phone Log. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Ferry II and III. End Loader. Meeting and Phone Log. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Vendor Contact Lists. End Loader. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry Service. I, II, III. - Port Market Research. 1986 (Box 39)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Historical Research. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Sharp Specs. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Pricing Sheets. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Pricing Summary. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Item Sheets. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Codes. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Interior Design. Basic Vessel. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Changeover Designs. 3. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Memorandum. Food Service. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Audio Visual Systems. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Memorandum. Video Programming. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Memorandum. Harbor Tours. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Research. Food Service. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Photographs. Background. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Bulkhead Panels. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Carpet. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Ceiling System. Framing. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Dancefloor. Stage. Chairs. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Deck Underlayment. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Electric Signs. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Flooring. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry I. 1986. - Hardware. 1986 (Box 40)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Hopeman Brothers. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Ferry. Lighting. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Logo. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Mesh. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Railings. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Plumbing. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Portable Toilets. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Partitions. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Skylights. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Special Events Items. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Toilets. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Variety Scenic Studio. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Video. Sound. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Windows. Doors. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Exterior Paint. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Vehicles. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Concept. Reports. Costs. Book 1. 1986. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Item Sheets, Cuts, Sketches. Book 2. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Originals. Book 2. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry II. 1986. - Originals. Book 1. 1986 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. 1987 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Phone and Meeting Log Book. 1987 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Press and Public Relations. 1987 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Transmittals. 1987 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Memorandum. 1987 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Business. 2 folders. 1987 (Box 41)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Volume II Detail Drawings. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Capital Cost Estimate. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Prototype Pricing. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Item Sheets. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Styling Design. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Interior Design. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Changeover Design. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Food Service Program. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Audio Vision Program. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Harbor Tour Programs. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Off-Peak Programming. Background. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Lighting. general. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Lighting. Off Peak. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Fiberglass Bulkheads. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Carpet Options. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Door and Bath Hardware. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Seating and Lockdown. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Seating Options. general. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Seating Options. American. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Seating Options. Beiffe. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Seating Options. Coach and Car. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Seating Options. Kinetics. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Seating Options. Kroin. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Seating Options. Rudd. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Photographs. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry IV. - Sound. Off Peak. 1988 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. 1986 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Item Information Sheets. Book 2. 1986 (Box 42)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Interim Report. Book. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Report. Book 1. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Report. Book 2. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Ferry IV: Sample Board. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Business. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Port Authority Proposal. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Original Mail Packs. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Research. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Project Budget Tracking. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Memorandum. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Appendix. Book 2. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Appendix. Book 1. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Report. Book 1. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Final Report. Book 1. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Final report. Volume I. Revised 10/24/86. 1986 (Box 43)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Final Report 7/01/86. 1986 (Box 44)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Final report. 1986 (Box 44)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Final Report and Originals. Xerox of Volume II final. 1986 (Box 44)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Sample Books. Rockwool. TNF Manual. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Gibraltar Carpets. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Dampa Marine. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Moss Rose Fabrics. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - American Seating Chips. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Pauluhn. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Divinycell. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - USG Expanded Metals. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Aluminum Tube. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Cast Concrete. Custom Castings. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Cast Gypsum. Custom Castings. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Wittman Fiberglass. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Ceiling Light Eggcrate. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Roto Locks. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Karistan Carpet. 1987 (Box 45)
  - George Sharp. Trans-Hudson Ferry. - Allstate Rubber. 1987 (Box 45)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - "L". Transparency. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - Korea. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - Japan Treaty. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - WWII. Pearl Harbor. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - WWI Byrd. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - Time Between Wars. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - 1900 to WWI. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - Spanish American War. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - Civil War. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - Japan 1854. Perry. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - China 1842. Kear. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - War of 1812. Perry. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - J.P. Jones. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - "H". Transparency. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - "G". Transparency. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research Not Used. - Women Current. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Specials. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Credits. Negatives. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Transition to film. Transparency. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Homecoming. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - The People. Transparency. ships. planes. submarines. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Special Services. Transparency. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Training. Transparency. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Embark. Transparence. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Flag Raising. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Vietnam. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Korea. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Japan Treaty. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Pearl Harbor. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - WWI Byrd. 1987 (Box 46)